请系好安全带
Would you put your seat back, please?
请系好安全带...
Would you fasten your seat belt, please?
不好意思...
Excuse me. Excuse me.
请再来一杯行吗?
Can I get another one of those, please?
抱歉先生  我们20分钟 后就降落了
I'm sorry, sir. We'll be landing in 20 minutes.
但20分钟也很漫长啊
Well, 20 minutes is a long time.
干嘛不读读报纸呢?
How about a newspaper instead?
请系好你的安全带
And if you could buckle your seat belt, sir...
很抱歉  我们的飞机在飞往 洛杉矶过程中遇到暖流  故有些震动
Sorry about the bumps,folks.We're just hitting a little warm air as we make our descent into Los Angeles.
请系好你的安全带 我们的飞机即将降落
Please keep those seat belts fastened,and we'll have you on the ground shortly.
本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
仅供学习交流之用 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
欢迎访问YYeTs美剧论坛进行交流 www.YYETS.com
■
翻译：   许愿  后期：梁良  双语字幕：七色九天
现在无法接通310-555-0148这个电话
You can't reach the 310-555-0148
请留言...
Please leave a message.
是我
It's me.
我...我刚看到...
I...I just read...
请宽恕我...
Forgive me.
妈妈! 妈妈! 妈妈!
Mom! Mom! Mom!
-救命  -妈妈!
-Help!  -Mom!
-要的都准备齐全了吗?  -没 但能利用的都利用到了
-You have everything you need?  -No,but I made the best out of what we have.
-Bernard和Jin?  -他们都很准  而且也很积极
-Bernard and Jin?  -They're both excellent shots and highly motivated.
炸药放在那里 我们不会失手的
The dynamite's in place. We won't miss.
Jack 不论这里发生什么事 你都要继续前进
Jack,No matter what happens here,I want you to keep moving.
带他们去无线电塔
Keep moving for that radio tower.
不要以任何理由回来
Don't turn back for any reason.
我宁愿牺牲也要让 大家安全得救
I'm willing to give my life if it means securing rescue,
可我不想白白送死
but I'm not giving it up for nothing.
你明白吗?
You understand?
是的
yeah
我明白
I understand.
祝你好运
Then good luck.
你也是
You, too.
如果我告诉你我愿意帮你搭 那个SOS标记  你会改变主意吗?
If I told you that I'd help you with your "S.O.S." sign,would you change your mind?
不会的  女士
No, ma'am.
我要你再说一遍
I want you to say it again.
-Rose...  -说啊 Bernard...
-Rose...  -Say it, Bernard...
我只是个牙医 我不是兰博
I am a dentist. I am not Rambo.
你可别忘了
And don't you forget it.
Charlie会没事的
Charlie's gonna be fine.
是啊
Yeah.
当然咯....
Of course he is.
和Jack待在一起 如果累了就停下来休息
Jin...
你为什么要这样做?
因为...我们要...回家
Because...we have... to go... home.
好了
Alright.
我们出发吧!
Let's do it.
Jack 能问你个问题吗?
Jack,can I ask you a question?
当然
Sure
在你变成土著人之前 你是干什么的?
What did you do for a living before you became Moses?
我是一个医生
I was a doctor.
那当然咯
Right. 'course you were.
我想让你看看这个  医生
Well, I need your attention for a minute, doctor.
她没关系吧?
Is she okay?
为什么这样说?
Why wouldn't she be?
因为大家都不信任她
Because none of your people trusts her.
我不是针对你
No offense.
那我先走了 你们慢慢跟上
Why don't you catch up to me when you're done?
-Juliet...  -没关系的
-Juliet...  -It's fine.
我想让你知道这小玩意是怎么用的 如果我发生了什么事
So I need to show you how this wonderful gadget works,in case anything happens to me.
你可以使用它来 联络我的船
You need to be able to call my boat.
好啊
Okay. Show me.
当然也很简单
It's actually simple.
按这里打开
Turn her on here.
这个将打开 连通货船的直接频道
This opens a direct channel to the freighter.
按这里  然后听到拨号音...
Give her a tap here. Wait for the beep
你就可以说话了
and say hello.
没错
That's it.
一旦摇滚巨星把水下的 那个阻挠系统关闭...
Once the rock star turns off whatever underwater contraption is jamming us up,
这个红色的灯就会变绿
this red light will turn a lovely shade of green.
这随时都会发生 是吗?
That'll be any time now, yeah?
希望如此
Hopefully.
你是谁?
Who are you?
如果你告诉我们你是 怎么下来的  我们就不会伤害你
If you tell us how you got down here,we won't hurt you.
我乘着隐型潜艇来
I came in my invisible submarine.
你看不出来吗?
Don't you see it?
你冷静点!
Take it easy.
冷静?  他是他们的人
Take it easy? He's one of them.
你为什么来这里?
Why are you here?
你是怎么知道这个站的?
How did you find out about this station?
Juliet告诉我们的
Juliet told us.
她现在和我们是一伙的了
She's one of us now.
你没有听说吗?
In case you haven't heard.
住手!
Stop!
我们通知Ben吧
We gotta call Ben.
你最好通知Ben
Let's call Ben.
来吧
Come on.
有个装着很多仪器的房间
You're inside a room full of equipment.
有个闪着黄灯的开关
There's a blinking yellow light above a switch.
你扳动了开关 灯就灭了
You flick the switch.Light goes off.
然后你就被淹死了...
And you drown...
Ben快接啊 Ben
Ben,come in,Ben
Ben 我是Bonnie...Ben 你在吗?
It's Bonnie. Ben,are you there?
能听见我吗 Ben?
Can you hear me?
到底发生了什么事?
Why are you breaking radio silence?
他们中的一个人在这里
One of them's down here.
你说什么?
I'm sorry. What?
我们绑着他  他们中的一个人在这里...
We've got him tied up, but he's here.One of them swam down here.
谁?  哪个人?
Who? Which one?
他不肯告诉我们
He won't tell us.
Charlie!  向Ben问声好
It's Charlie! Tell him I said hi!
他是怎么知道那里的?
How did...How does he know about the station.
他说Juliet告诉他的
He said Juliet told them.
待着别动  别做任何事 我去叫增援
All right, sit tight. Don't do anything.I'm sending help.
Mikhail 你下去那里 查清Charlie在那里干什么
You need to go down to the Looking Glass
and find out what Charlie Pace is doing down there.
你告诉我们"守望镜" 已经被毁了...
You told us the Looking Glass was inoperable...
都淹了...
flooded.
我撒了谎
I lied.
Mikhail 我要你现在就去!
Mikhail, I need you to go now!
黄昏前应该能到
I can be there by dawn.
如果Juliet告诉他们"守望镜"  她还会告诉他们什么?
But if Juliet told them about the Looking Glass,what else did she tell them?
Ryan 你听到吗...
Ryan, come in.
Ryan 你在吗?
Ryan, are you there?
-对讲机都关了吗?  -是的
-Are your walkies all off?  -Yes, sir.
都看清楚了吗?
Did you get a good look?
3个帐篷都做上了 白色的标记
The tents are marked with white coral... three of'em.
Juliet干的真出色
Juliet did her job.
我们行动吧
Alright. Let's do this.
里面是空的!
It's empty!
离帐篷远点!
Get away from the tent!
-是个陷阱 快撤!  -上帝啊!
-It's a trap! Move!  -Please, God.
撤  我们撤!
Move, move!
在树那边!
The tree line!
我抓住你们的人了  把枪放下!
I got your man!Drop your weapons!
我抓住他了  都结束了!
I got your man! It's over!
你敢扣下扳机!
Don't.Finger off the trigger.
应该有三次爆炸才对
There were supposed to be three explosions.
看来没有成功
It didn't work.
-没事了 都弄好了  -谢谢
-There you go. Good as new.  -Thanks.
媒体的人都等在外面 你是个大英雄
The news people are waiting for you outside,you being a hero and all.
很好
Right.
那个女人  她怎么样了?
The woman... how is she?
她情况很稳定 多亏了你在那桥上
She's been stabilized.Thank God you were on that bridge.
是啊...
yeah...
抱歉  急诊室不允许探访
Sorry. No visitors in E.R.
没关系  她是我的前妻
It's okay.She's...We used to be married.
那进来吧
Come on in.
发生什么事了?
What happened?
是...
There was...
一起车祸
a car accident.
你没事吧?
Are you okay?
是的  我很好
Yeah, I'm fine.
你又喝多了吧?
Were you drinking again?
-是吗 Jack?  -没有!
-Are you, Jack?  -No.
你为什么来这里 Sarah?
Why did you come down here, Sarah?
我还是你的紧急联系人
I'm still listed as your emergency contact.
你当时在做什么 凌晨两点还在外面开车?
What were you doing driving around at 2:00 in the morning?
你能载我回家吗?
Maybe you could give me a lift home?
我想这不大合适
I don't think that would be appropriate.
是啊...
yeah...
那...
Well...
谢谢你来这里 Sarah
Thanks for coming down,Sarah.
再见 Jack
Goodbye,Jack.
为什么只有两次爆炸?
Why were there only two explosions?
也许他们不需要引爆 第三个帐篷
Maybe they didn't have to blow the 3rd tent.
-但那里枪声是怎么回事?  -他不会有事的 Rose
But those gunshots...What was that about?  -He's okay.
你这么认为吗?
Do you believe that?
他们根本毫无防备
Listen,they had no idea that we were waiting for them,
而且Sayid也和他们在一起 他们会没事的  几小时后就能赶上我们
and Sayid's with your husbands.They're gonna
be fine,and they're gonna be a couple hours behind us.
-那我们等在这里  你先走...  -不行!
-We should wait for them here.You go...  -No.
谁也不能留在这里
No one gets left behind.
如果你对我说"同生独死"的话 Jack  我会给你一巴掌
If you say,"live together, die alone" to me,I'm gonna punch you in your face.
这很公平 Rose
Fair enough, Rose.
这很公平
Fair enough.
但我们有计划
But we have a plan!
我们现在知道  我们成功了
And for all we know, it worked.
没事的  会好起来的
It's gonna be okay.Everything is gonna be all right.
我们继续前进好吗?
Let's just keep moving, okay?
没关系的  我们走...
It's okay. Let's go.
我再问你一遍
I'm gonna ask you this one more time.
你为什么来这里?
Why are you here?
我来这里...
I'm here...
是来关掉你们的阻挠系统 就在那个黄灯的旁边
to turn off your jamming equipment.In there,next to the flashing yellow light.
-你是怎么知道这些的?  -我就是知道呗
-Now how'd you know about that?  -I know because I know.
不管你们想对我怎么样 我都要关了它
Whatever you ladies do to me,I'm going to turn it off.
- 是吗?  - 一点没错
- You are, huh?   - Most definitely am.
那密码是什么?
So what's the code?
什么?
What?
如果你想要关掉它 你还需要一个密码
If you're gonna turn off the jamming equipment,you're gonna need the code,
只有3个人知道  我  她  还有Ben
and only three people know it. Me,her and Ben.
那...
Well...
我不需要什么密码 当这个站被淹掉后...
Guess I won't need the code...Since this entire station's gonna be flooded anyway.
只要关掉那个开关 直升机就会来救我的朋友了
Now just turn off your little jammer,and the
helicopters come and rescue all my friends.
如果这个站淹了...
But if this station floods,
那你又会怎么样?
what happens to you?
我死了呗...
I die...
什么?
What?
他们都死了 Diane  Ivan 都死了!
They're all dead, Diane, Ivan. All of them dead.
但Shephard和他的人都走了!
It's Shephard and his people, they're gone!
-走?  去哪里了?  -我不知道  你没听我说吗?
-Gone? Gone where?  -I don't know. Did you hear me?
-他们杀了我们7个...  -冷静一下  告诉他好消息
-They killed seven of us...  -Calm down and tell him the good news.
什么好消息?
What good news?
我们抓住了 3个留下引爆帐篷的人
We caught three of them...The ones that stayed behind to blow up the tents.
他们知道我们会来
They knew we were coming.
是Juliet  她背叛了我们.
It was Juliet. She betrayed us.
什么?!  查一下她现在在哪里 Tom
What? Just figure out where she is,Tom.
起来!
Get up.
好了  童子军  他们...
Okay, junior, where the hell did...
他们不肯说
They're not talking.
-他们是谁?  -Jarrah Kwon还有那个牙医  -杀了Kwon
-Who do you have?  -Jarrah, Kwon and the dentist.  -Shoot Kwon.
-什么?  -你想让他们说话 就杀了kwon!
-What?  -You want them to answer questions, kill Kwon.
快开枪!
Do it now!
我不知道你在说什么 但一定很可爱
I don't know what that means,but I'm sure it's lovely.
不  等等! 不要!
No, wait, no...
不要说! 请别这样!
No talk. No, please.
快说  没有人会受伤的 快告诉我他们去哪里了?
Talk to me. Nobody will get hurt. Now tell me where your people went.
他在撒谎 他会杀了我们的....
He's lying. He's going to kill us all...
他们在哪里?
Where are they?
再见咯
sa yo na ra.
无线电塔
The radio tower.
他们去无线电塔了
They're hiking to a radio tower.
他们去那里干什么?
Why in the hell are they going there?
一个女人跳伞来到这里
A woman parachuted here.
她有个卫星电话 他们要和她的船联络
She has a satellite phone,and they're gonna call her ship.
Juliet认为我们明天才来
Juliet thought we were coming tomorrow,
为什么今晚他们等着我们呢?
so why were they waiting for us tonight?
你听见他说的了
You heard him.
你们是怎么知道的?
How'd you know?
一个孩子
A kid
告诉我们的 他来警告我们
told us.He came in a canoe and warned us.
什么孩子?
What kid?
Karl  他叫Karl
Karl. He said his name was Karl.
你听见了吗 Ben?
You heard that, Ben?
Ben!
我听见了
I heard.
你要我们杀了他们吗?
What do you want us to do? Kill them?
不
No.
还不是时候
Not yet.
我们要去无线电塔?
We're going to the radio tower?
不是"我们" Richard  只有我
Not we, Richard. Me.
你照原计划带大家去神殿
You're going to take everyone to the temple as planned.
现在去可不是时候
Now might not be the best time to go tromping off on your own.
是吗?  为什么?
Really? And why not?
大家都议论纷纷 Ben
Because people are asking questions,
离开家园
about leaving home,
Locke的事  还有Jacob
about what happened to Locke,about Jacob.
更不用说那些谣言
Not to mention the rapidly spreading rumor
说去海滩的那些人都死了
that everyone who went down to the beach is dead.
他们没有全死
They're not all dead.
你要去哪里?
Where are you going?
你好啊 Alex
Hello, Alex.
我问你 你要去哪里
I asked where you were going.
我想去散散步
Well, I thought I might go for a walk,
看能不能找到Jack和他的朋友们
see if I can't find Jack and all his friends.
我要和你一起去
I'm coming with you.
好啊
Alright.
-什么?  -我说好啊
-What?  -I said alright.
这是个不错的主意
In fact, I think it's a good idea.
你很想再见到Karl 是吗?
I mean, you do wanna see Karl again,don't you?
快收拾一下 我们10分钟后就出发
Get your pack.I'm leaving in ten minutes.
他们有40个人 你只有一个人
There're 40 of them,and you're alone.
他们会不惜一切代价 离开这座岛的
They're gonna do whatever it takes to get off the island.
你去那里又能怎么样呢?
What do you think is gonna happen when you get there?
我会和他们谈妥的
I'm gonna talk them out of it.
有些不对劲
Something's wrong.
很多事都不对劲
Lots of things are wrong.
Jin  Bernard  Sayid 他们现在应该已经赶上我们了
Jin, Bernard, Sayid...They should've caught up to us by now.
我要回去看看他们是否安全了
I wanna go back to make sure they're all right.
当然咯
'course you do.
你这是什么意思?
What's that supposed to mean?
我的意思是Kate 总有人要回去的
It means, Kate,there's always someone to go back for.
-你到底怎么了?  -没什么
-What's the matter with you?  -Nothing.
-没事吗?  -我很好
-Nothing?  -I'm fine.
怎么不告诉我 发生了什么事?
Why don't you just tell me what happened?
-你这是干什么? -让你清醒清醒
-What'd you do that for?  -To wake you up.
自从你从Locke那边回来 你就像梦游一样
Ever since you got that tape from Lock,it's like you've been sleepwalking.
你不在乎我们的朋友 那没关系
You don't care about our friends, fine,
但你好像什么都不在乎了
but it's like you don't care about anything anymore.
还有从什么时候开始 你叫我"Kate"了?
And since when did you start calling me "Kate"?
你知道
You know...
他们派Juliet来检查Sun
They sent Juliet to check out Sun.
但她来也想检查我 是否也怀孕了
But she was there to check and see if I'm pregnant, too.
我们希望你没有吧
Well, let's hope you're not.
灯还是红的吗?
That light still red?
Des!  Des!
妈的 你还好吗?
Bloody hell. You all right?
如果你不走 我就惨了
Not for long if you don't get out of here.
你必须躲起来Des  快躲起来 那里面有人
You have to hide.There's people in there.
快藏起来  快快快快!!
Quick, hide, hide!
他在和谁说话?
Who's he talking to?
"Acting like it's stupid stupid people wearing..."
你在和谁说话?
Who were you talking to?
没有啊
Wasn't talking to anyone.
我只是在唱歌
I was just singing.
"You all everybody"
闭嘴
Shut up.
好吧
Right, okay. You got it.
进来
Come on.
需要帮助吗?
Can I help you?
只是在看她的受伤状况
Just checking her chart.
抱歉  我是Hamill Rob医生
I'm sorry. I'm Dr. Hamill...Rob.
我是这里的新外科主任医师 我想我们还没见过面
The new chief of surgery. I don't think we've met yet.
Jack  Shephard
Shephard医生 那个英雄
Dr. Shephard, the hero...
已经两次了
Twice over.
你还好吗?
You all right?
经过昨晚这么一折腾 你还来继续工作啊
After last night,I'm surprised you'd even wanna come in.
说起正确的时间地点
Talk about right place, right time, huh?
这个女人很幸运有你在场
This woman is very lucky you were there.
如果她够幸运 她的背就不会骨折了
If she was lucky,she wouldn't have a fractured back
她的脊椎受到了严重的外伤
that was impinging upon her spinal cord.
我想一早就给她做手术
I'd like to...operate first thing in the morning.
你想做手术?
You wanna operate?
是的
Yes.
很抱歉  但她不是你的病人
I'm sorry, but this isn't your patient,
她的情况我们都了解  Gary Nadler 6点会给她做手术
and we are well aware of the issues.Gary Nadler's doing the surgery at 6:00 a.m.
请恕我直言
With all due respect...
Hamill医生  但我还是 想自己来做
Dr.Hamill, I'd rather do it myself.
昨晚
Last night,
你把这个女人8岁的孩子 从着火的车里拉了出来
you pulled this woman's 8-year-old son out of a flaming car,
然后又跑去救她
then you went back for her.
我想你做的够多的了
I think you've done enough.
我想做这次手术
I wanna do the surgery.
一切都在掌握之中
Look, everything's under control here.
她会没事的
She'll be fine.
回家吧
Go home.
去喝一杯
Have a drink.
这是你应得的
You deserve it.
情况表 Jack
The chart, please.
你随时打电话给我
You call me.
我想了解情况
I wanna know what happens.
今晨  第6大街的这座桥 被关闭了几小时
This morning,the bridge of six avenue was shut down for several hours
这里发生了车祸 有两名伤者
in the wake of a fiery car accident that left two injured.
一名40岁的女士和她的儿子
An unidentified 40-year-old woman and her son.
他们很幸运
Fortunately for the two of them,
Jack Shephard医生就在现场
Dr.Jack Shephard was near the scene of the crash
他把两个人拉出了 着火的车子
and pulled both victims from the burning wreckage
然后对他们进行了急救 直到救护车的到来
and treated them at the scene until paramedics arrived.
伤者稍后被转到St.Sebastian医院
The victims were later transported to St. Sebastian hospital.
目前还没有最新情况
Further details of their conditions have not yet been released.
我回去吧
I'm going back.
什么?
What?
我回去海滩那里
I'm going back to the beach.
这不行
No way.
我们得继续前进
We keep moving.
我可不指望得到许可
I ain't asking permission.
你有事要做
Look, you got a job to do here.
我不会碍事的 你在这里也不需要我
I ain't gonna stand in your way of doing it,but you sure as hell don't need me.
你认为你孤身一人 又不带武器过去 能够搞定?
What do you think you're gonna get done,alone and unarmed?
-我和他一起去  -不行
-He won't be alone.I'll go with him.  -No.
20分钟前你还不想回去
20 mins ago,you weren't even interested in going,
-现在你突然告诉Jack...  -我不想和你一起去
-and now all of a sudden,you're telling Jack...  -I didn't wanna go with you.
没枪的话就只是去送死
It's a suicide mission without guns.
我知道哪里有枪
I know where there are some guns.
离这里几英里的地方 有个隐藏地点
There's a hidden cache a couple of miles from here.
我们去海滩的路上 能顺便去下那里
I can take us back to the beach on a route past it.
Juliet 你不必这么做的
Juliet, you don't have to do that.
是的 Jack  我要这么做
Yeah, Jack, I kinda do.
我们走吧
Let's do this.
别干傻事
Don't do anything stupid.
如果你不做的话
I won't if you won't.
别等我们
Don't wait up.
我叫你闭嘴!
I told you to shut up!
你知道一个曲子 一直萦绕在脑海里
You know how you get a tune stuck in your head?
这首歌就会让你 有灵感了
This song...It just started coming to me.
如果找到桥的话 就完成了
It's almost finished.Just need to find the bridge.
-拿叉枪来  -什么? 为什么?
-Get the speargun.  -What? Why?
因为我想搞点伤害
'Cause I want it to hurt.
-不  Ben说我们...  -你不去  我去
-No, Ben said we...  -You don't wanna get it? I will.
Bonnie
好好好  我闭嘴!
No. I'll... I'll shut up!
我闭嘴!  一定闭嘴!
I'll shut up,I'll shut up
Mikhail?
我还以为你们在加拿大
I thought you two were on assignment in Canada.
他让我们承诺不告诉任何人
He made us promise not to tell anyone.
-你好啊   -另一个人在哪里?
-Hello again.  -Where is the other one?
-什么?  -那个白痴跳下了船
-What?  -This idiot swam down from a boat.
我刚向他的朋友开了枪
I was just shooting at his friend.
他潜水下来了 只有他一个人
He dove down here. He's alone.
你确定吗?
Are you sure about that?
我有个更好的问题  电磁人
Here's a better question to ask, Cyclops.
为什么你们的小朋友Ben 告诉你们这个站被淹了?
Why did your little friend Ben tell you people that this entire station was flooded when it isn't?
还有为什么这两个人 一直在阻挠这里的信号?
Or, why these two have been jamming transmissions off the island?
什么?
What?
是真的吗?
Is that true?
-那是Ben  -我来和他说
-That's Ben.  -I'll get it.
你要明白  我做的一切 都是为了这座岛
You have to understand.Everything I did,I did for the island.
这座岛告诉你你能 欺骗自己的人吗?
The island told you it was necessary for you to jam your own people?
我也没办法
Yes, it did.
你一直都很忠诚 Mikhail 现在你要相信我
You've always been a loyalist, Mikhail.Now I'm asking you to trust me,
相信Jacob  是他 告诉我这样做的
to trust Jacob who told me to do that.
Jacob让你对自己人撒谎?
Why would Jacob ask you to lie to your own people?
因为这座岛一直受到强大力量 的袭击  未来我们也必须这样做
cos this island's under assault by
forces stronger than anything it's had to deal with in many,many years,
所以我们要保护它  不惜一切代价
and we are meant to protect it,by any means necessary.
阻挠信号是为了大家的安全
The jamming was for everyone's security.
我们的处境很危险
We are in a serious situation here.
为什么不信任我?
So why not trust me?
我犯了个错误
I made a mistake.
我应该告诉你的 我向你道歉
I should have told you, and I apologize.
Mikhail 你还在吗?
Mikhail, are you still there?
是的
Yes.
我需要你的帮助
I need you to help me.
我要你弥补我的过失
I need you to help me clean up this mess that I've made.
我要你杀了Charlie
I need you to kill Charlie.
确保干扰设备继续正常运转
Make sure that the jamming mechanism continues to function at all cost.
我们不能冒险让Greta和Bonnie 告诉其他人这件事
And we can't risk Greta and Bonnie telling the others what we've done,
所以把他们也一起解决了
so you'll have to take care of them, too.
我怎么才能相信你对 他们说的也是这一套?
How do I know you didn't say the same thing to them about me?
因为我说了的话 Mikhail 你早就没命了
Because if I had, Mikhail...you'd already be dead.
你还好吗?
You okay?
没事  只是...
Yeah, I just...
鞋里有块石头
got a rock in my shoe.
他不是那个意思
He didt mean it, you know.
-什么?  -Sawyer
-What?  -Sawyer.
他说他不想跟你一起回去 他不是那个意思
When he said that he didn't want you to go with him... he didn't mean it.
如果他不是那个意思 他干嘛那么说?
If he didn't mean it, why'd he say it?
他只是想保护你
He was trying to protect you.
这也就是我叫你 别回来找我的原因
That's why I asked you not to come back for me.
你干嘛要替Sawyer说话?
Why are you sticking up for Sawyer?
他绝不会替你说话
He'd never do it for you.
因为我爱你
Because I love you.
把我们赶出关熊的笼子 然后把我们锁在一起
Out of those polar bear cages and put us on the chain gang,
还有为什么让我们 打碎那些石头呢?
what the hell did you have us breaking all those rocks for, anyway?
我们在建跑道
We were building a runway.
跑道?  干嘛用的?
A runway? For what?
那些外星人
The aliens.
我也不知道 你以为他们什么都告诉我吗?
I don't know what for.Do you think they told me everything?
随便你说吧
Yeah, yeah, whatever you say.
-你和Jack上过床了吗?  -没有
-So you screwing Jack yet?  -No.
你呢?
Are you?
离那些枪还有多远?
How far away are these guns?
根本没什么枪
There aren't any guns.
什么?
What?
-我撒了谎  -你撒谎
-I lied.  -You lied.
这是他能让我们 回来的唯一借口
It was the only way he'd let us go back.
你为什么要回来
So why are you going back?
因果报应吧
Karma.
你又什么要回来呢 James?
Why are you going back, James?
伙计们  等一下!
Hey, guys! Wait up!
你想干什么?
What the hell do you want?
我想和你们一起去
I'm coming with you guys.
不行
No way. Not a chance.
拜托  我能帮上忙的
Come on. I can help.
他们也是我的朋友
They're my friends, too, man.
Charlie不肯让我和他们去
Charlie wouldn't let me go with him,
Jack在那边忙得没空和我说话
and Jack's too busy leading to even talk to me.
我只是想帮下忙  好吗?
I just wanna help. Please?
看在上帝的份上Hugo  瞧瞧你 你只会拖累我们
For God sakes, Hugo, look at you!You're just gonna get in the way.
你想让我们全死啊?
You wanna get us killed?
走吧
Come on.
如果我们朝北走 我们可以在他们之前到塔那里
If we head north,we should get to them before they reach the tower.
为什么让我一起来?
Why did you let me come?
我让你来是想把你 交托给一个新的家庭
I let you come because I'm delivering you to your new family.
我让你来是因为你背叛了我
I let you come because you betrayed me.
你把Karl关在笼子里
You locked Karl in a cage.
还把他关在那个房间里 给他洗脑
You put him in a room and tried to brainwash him.
我不想让你怀孕
I didn't want him to get you pregnant.
我想我反应过度了
I suppose I overreacted.
我们最好现在就上路
We'd better get going.
你为什么要阻止他们?
Why do you have to stop them?
就不能让他们走吗?
Why won't you just let them leave?
因为我不能 Alex
Because I can't, Alex.
别这样 John
Don't, John.
把枪放下
Put the gun down.
-Walt?  -起来John
-Walt?  -Now get up, John.
他朝我开枪 我的腿动不了了
He shot me, and I can't...move my legs.
你能的
You can move your legs.
快从坑里爬起来
Now get out of the ditch.
为什么?
Why?
因为你还有事要去做
Because you have work to do.